Hey.
（岡崎(おかざき)）いや…
Come on.
いや だから！
It's not just my fault.
それは僕だけのせいじゃ ないですよね？
Right now,
今…
I'm with Miho.
美穂(みほ)さんと 一緒にいるんです
Listen. This isn't just my problem.
いいですか？ これは 僕だけの問題じゃない
This is our problem.
“僕たち”の問題ですよね？
Right?
そうですよね？
Okay.
はい
Take care of this, Director.
よろしくお願いしますよ 理事長
I'm back.
お待たせ
So, what do you want to do?
ん〜 どうしようかな
You must be hungry.
おなか すいてるでしょ？
What do you want to eat?
何か食べたいものとか ある？
Well, okay. Why don't we see a movie?
うん じゃあ 何か映画でも見に行こっか？
Miho.
美穂
It isn't easy when a friend dies. It would make anyone sad.
そりゃ 友達が死んだら 誰だって悲しいさ
But you see,
けど 僕はね
I like to see you happy, Miho.
美穂の笑顔が好きなんだよね
So,
だから…
I want you to be happy when you're with me.
僕といるときは 美穂には笑顔でいてほしい
I understand.
（美穂）そうだね
I need to be optimistic.
前に進まないと
Right. Okay, let's get something to eat.
よし じゃあ とりあえず 飯 食べに行こう
How about that café?
あの 昔 行ったカフェ
That place with the view of the ocean.
あの 海の見えるレストラン
You remember, right?
ほら 覚えてるでしょ？
Let's go there.
あそこ 行こう
Okay.
よいしょ
She had a strong sense of justice.
正義感の強い子だったの
She should have lived long but she's dead now,
死ななくていい人間が死んで
while people who should be dead are still alive.
死ねばいい人間が生きてるなんて 間違ってる
Anyway, let's go.
とにかく行こう
More. This world needs more.
もっと もっと もっと…
This world needs more justice.
真っ白にしてやる この世界を
I've had enough.
（愛奈(まな)）もうやだ
I don't care what happens now.
っていうか もう どうでもいい
Don't talk like that.
（芽実(めみ)）そんなこと言わないでよ
I'm fed up!
（愛奈）もう限界！
Get rid of someone! I don't care who!
誰でもいいから もう早く落として！
Quit shouting!
（京子(きょうこ)）わめくなよ！
If Mr. Hayashi didn't bring us here,
（芽実） 私たちを ここに連れてきたのが 林(はやし)先生じゃないなら
then who did?
一体 誰だっていうの？
I thought we would be forgiven if we confessed about Perfect,
（久美(くみ)） マッシロのこと 告白すれば許してもらえる…
but it didn't work.
そう思ってたのに
What's under this floor?
（彩花(あやか)） この床の下 一体どうなってんの！
Where was Mr. Hayashi taken?
林先生は どこに落とされたの！
Ayaka.
（京子）彩花…
What about those weird screams and that earthquake?
（芽実） 変な声はするし 地震は起こるし…
I don't think that was an earthquake.
（美玲(みれい)）地震の揺れとは違うと思う
And those screams sounded like something scraping,
それに あの悲鳴 何かが きしむ音だと思う だから…
-so... -So what?
だから！
Who cares where we are?
ここが どこだなんて もう どうでもいいって！
-Mana! -What?
（芽実）愛奈！ （愛奈）何よ！
Mr. Hayashi tried to destroy that mounted deer head.
（美玲） 先生 あの剥製を壊そうとしてた
Is there someone
あの向こう…
watching us through it?
誰かがいる？
Mr. Hayashi said,
先生が言ってた
"Whatever you look at, it reminds you of something."
“何を見ても何かを思い出す”
that's the only way.
それしかない
Mana, let's work together.
愛奈 一緒に頑張ろう
Okay?
ね？
Let's all get out of here.
ここから出よう
A medical book?
医学書？
There are many pictures of sisters.
姉妹の絵が多いね
Sisters?
姉妹？
You're right. I hadn't noticed.
ホントだ　全然 気が付かなかった
They look like they get along,
（彩花）仲 良さそうに見えるけど
but they all look kind of sad.
何だか みんな悲しそうな目してる
Look at that one.
その絵
This one?
これ？
I think I've seen it before.
どっかで見たことある気がする
-Really? -Quit making things up.
（彩花）え？ （京子）お前…
Hold on. Let me think where I have seen it.
（芽実） ちょっと待って 今 思い出すから
Hurry up and remember.
（京子）早く思い出せよ （テーブルを軽くたたく音）
-Hurry. -Be quiet!
（京子）早く （芽実）ちょっと黙って
Hurry up and remember.
（京子）早く思い出せよ （テーブルを軽くたたく音）
-Wait! -What?
（芽実）あ！ （京子）お？
It's no good. I can't remember.
ダメだ 思い出せない
-Seriously? -Are you kidding me?
（彩花）はあ？ （京子）お前 ふざけんなよ
What?
（美玲）え？
Look at this!
見て！
I can't see that.
全然 見えねえよ！
What?
（彩花）え！
Seriously?
マジかよ？
Let us see it too.
（芽実）ねえ 私たちにも見せて！ （テーブルを軽くたたく音）
That's the picture.
（芽実）そう この絵！
Why is that here?
（彩花）どういうこと？
Isn't that...
（芽実）この場所って…
Okazaki's place.
（久美）岡崎さん
Right, the villa of Miho's boyfriend.
あっ 美穂の彼氏… の別荘
When was that?
（彩花）いつだっけ？
Wasn't it the Golden Week?
あ〜 ゴールデンウィークとかだっけ？
But why is that painting here?
（久美） でも なんで そこにあった絵が ここにあるの？
Mirei.
（彩花）美玲 美玲！
Forget it. She's in the zone again.
（京子） ダメだ また変なモードに入った
It was the same seven people as now.
今いる７人と 一緒
What?
（京子）え？
Remember?
あの日…
We're the ones who were with Miho at the villa.
美穂と 一緒に 別荘に行ったメンバー
The seven of us.
ここにいる７人だよ
Seriously?
（京子）そんな…
It's just a coincidence.
偶然だろ？
Ayaka.
（美玲）彩花
Kyoko.
京子
Kumi.
久美
Memi.
芽実
Mana.
愛奈
Shiho.
史帆(しほ)
Me.
私
That means,
つまり…
it was planned that we would be the only ones left.
この７人になるように 仕組んだ誰か
That's...
それが…
-Are you saying it's Okazaki? -Impossible.
（京子） 岡崎が犯人だっていうのか！
Then why is that same painting here?
じゃあ なんで同じ絵が ここにあるの？
For revenge.
（美玲）復讐(ふくしゅう)
We're the ones
自分の彼女…
who bullied his girlfriend, Miho, and forced her to disappear.
美穂をいじめて 失踪に追い込んだ私たちへの
I don't think Okazaki has anything to do with this.
岡崎さんは関係ないと思う
What? Did you say something?
ん？ 何か言った？
This is a video from back then.
あのときの動画
Thank you.
（史帆） ありがとう
Yes!
（久美たち） イエーイ
There you go. Do you like it?
（芽実） あっ 来た おいしい？
Yes! It's great!
（史帆） おいしい！ ヤバい！
You really like meat, Shiho.
（芽実） 史帆は肉食だもんね
Hey! What's that supposed to mean?
（史帆） え？ それ どういうこと？ もう！
-Do you want some? -Can I have it?
（史帆）食べる？ （芽実）え？ いいの？
Sure. Thanks.
（芽実） 食べる　ありがとう
Thank you.
いただきます
This is really good!
めっちゃ おいしい！
That's it?
（彩花）これだけ？
Well,
（芽実）え？
yes.
うん…
That's the first time I have heard Shiho's voice in a while.
（彩花）史帆の声 久々に聞いた
Hey, when did you stop talking?
（京子） あれ？ いつから しゃべんなくなったんだっけ？
Kyoko, give me the phone.
京子 スマホ　私も探してみる
I have one too.
私もあった
Hey, everyone. Listen up.
（岡崎） ちょっと あの… みんな いいかな？
What is this about?
（久美） 何だろ？
Stop eating.
（青年Ａ） 早く 食ってねえで
Miho, come here.
（岡崎） 美穂 ちょっと
Actually,
え〜と
one year ago on the same day,
実は今日 ５月３日は
On May 3rd, Miho and I started dating.
僕と美穂が 交際を始めてから
Seriously?
（青年Ａ）フー！ （青年Ｂ）マジ？
Miho, I hope to continue dating you.
（岡崎） 美穂 これからも よろしくね
Congratulations.
（美玲） おめでとう
-Congratulations.
（青年たち）おめでとう （拍手）
Thanks.
（美穂） ありがとう
Miho, smile for everyone.
（岡崎） 美穂 みんなのために笑って
What is wrong, Miho? You seem a little depressed.
どうしたの？ 美穂 あんま元気ないけど
Here's your favorite, Miho, hamburger. Have some.
あっ そうだ！ ほら 美穂の大好きな…
Oh, right.
そっか…
He's so conceited.
（京子）気取った野郎だな
That reminds me.
（彩花）そういえば…
He told me his parents have a yacht even though I never asked.
親が船 持ってるって 聞いてもいないのに自慢された
Seriously?
（京子）マジか…
I hate guys like that.
ホント そういう男 ムリ
Come to think of it,
（彩花）そもそも…
why did we go to his villa anyway?
なんで別荘に 行くことになったんだっけ？
Wasn't it Kumi who invited us?
（芽実） 確か 私たちに声かけたの 久美だったよね？
I organized it because Miho was really depressed then.
あのころ 美穂 落ち込んでたから…
She was?
そうだっけ？
A friend of ours died. She had been our friend since we were little.
美穂と私の幼なじみが 亡くなったの
A friend since you were little?
幼なじみって…
Is that the same person
さっき言ってた…
-who... -Who started Perfect?
（芽実）えっと… （京子）マッシロ始めた人？
Of course, I was shocked too when I heard about it.
私も聞いたときは もちろんショックだった
But Miho became really depressed.
でも 美穂は すごく落ち込んじゃってて…
So Okazaki and I decided to try cheering up Miho.
で 岡崎さんに相談して 美穂を元気づけようって…
Seriously?
（青年Ａ） マジか？
Miho.
（岡崎） 美穂
I swear
僕は生涯…
that I will love you for the rest of my life.
君を愛し続けることを 誓います
It's time to make a toast.
（青年Ａ） それでは…
Here's to the future director.
未来の理事長に…
Cheers!
乾杯！
-Cheers! -Congratulations!
（一同） 乾杯 おめでとう
Aren't you jealous?
（青年Ａ） 嫌みに感じない？
Let me see it, Miho.
（彩花） 美穂 見して
That's really pretty.
（青年Ａ） めっちゃ きれいだよ
-Looks good! -That's so nice!
（彩花） すごい
-I want to get married too. -That must have cost a lot.
（青年Ｃ） 俺も結婚したいな
However,
（久美）だけど…
after that day, Miho became even more depressed.
あの日のあと 美穂 もっと元気が なくなって…
Why?
え？ なんで？
She started accusing Okazaki of having another girlfriend.
（久美） 岡崎さんに“ほかに彼女が いるんじゃないか”って言い始めて
What a scumbag.
最低野郎だな
Can I say something?
（美玲）ちょっといい？
Mana, why have you been silent?
愛奈 さっきから なんで黙ってんの？
What?
（芽実）え？
What are you hiding?
お前 何 隠してんだよ！
-I'm not hiding anything. -Then show me that.
別に隠してない！
Quit accusing me!
変な言いがかりは やめてよ！
We aren't accusing you.
え？ いや…
What's wrong?
（芽実）どしたの？
It might help us get out of here.
何か ここから出れるヒントが あるかもしれないから
Okay, Mana?
ねっ 愛奈
There's nothing on my phone.
私のスマホには何もなかった
This is totally true.
これ すっごい事実！
See?
ほら
What's that about?
（京子） これが どうしたんだよ？
Mirei wore contacts on that day, instead of eyeglasses.
（愛奈） この日の美玲 眼鏡しないで
So?
（京子）はあ？
What about it?
（久美）それが どうしたの？
Look at her face.
（愛奈）いや この顔 見て！
She's acting all cutesy.
“ザ･女の子！”みたいな 顔してさ！
I wasn't! My glasses were broken that day.
違う！ その日は たまたま眼鏡が壊れてて…
-You look smart, but you're actually sly. -What does that have to do with anything?
知的な顔して 下心 見え見えで…
You started this, Mirei!
（愛奈） 美玲が言い始めたんでしょ！
What is with you two?
ちょっと ２人とも…
-What about you? -What?
（美玲）でもさ… （愛奈）何よ？
You were acting strange then, Mana.
（美玲） あのときの愛奈 何か変だった
What? I was?
は？ どこが？
What do you mean?
え？ どういう意味？
It's hard to explain.
何か 分からないけど
Hey, Mirei! Cut it out! Quit making things up!
（愛奈） ちょっと 美玲 やめて！ 適当なこと言わないでよ！
-Let me see your phone. -Give it back, Memi!
スマホ 見せてよ
-What? -Don't!
（芽実）なに？ （愛奈）やめて！
Give it back!
返して 返して！
Hey! That hurts!
（芽実）ちょっと 痛い 痛い！
I said, that hurts!
痛いってば
-Sorry. -That hurt.
（愛奈）ごめん （芽実）痛…
What's wrong with you, Mana?
愛奈 どうしたの？
Why are you so flustered?
なんで そんなに興奮してんの？
Was Okazaki cheating with you?
岡崎の浮気相手って お前か！
No! I wasn't!
違う 違う それは違う！
Hold on.
（美玲）ちょっと待って
I've remembered some things.
何か いろいろ思い出してきた
-On our way home that day... -Oh, yes!
（美玲）あの日の帰り… （彩花）そうだ
The bus was about to come,
バスが来る時間なのに
but Mana and Okazaki weren't there.
愛奈と岡崎さんだけ 見当たらなくて
Shut up!
やめて！
I remember too.
（京子）思い出した
Mana and Okazaki were late.
そしたら 愛奈と岡崎が遅れてきたんだ
No, we weren't!
それは違う！
It was you, right?
お前 まさか…
Are you serious?
え… うそでしょ？
I didn't do anything!
何もしてない！
Memi! We're best friends!
芽実 親友でしょ
Please! Help me!
お願い 助けて！
Come to think of it,
そういえば…
I remember your cheeks were flushed then.
あのときの愛奈の顔 火照(ほて)ってたかも…
Why would you say that?
なんで そんなこと言うの？
Wait. Hold on, you guys.
え… ちょっと待って
I swear! We didn't do anything!
ホントに何もないんだって！
Didn't Mana start bullying Miho
（彩花） 愛奈が美穂に いじめられ始めたのって
right after this barbecue?
このバーベキューの 直後じゃなかった？
Maybe Miho figured out her boyfriend was cheating on her with Mana.
美穂は 愛奈が自分の彼氏の 浮気相手だと知って…
You made me bully Miho because of that?
（芽実） そのせいで 私まで美穂に いじめられたわけ？
You dragged me into this
愛奈の浮気のせいで
because you were fooling around with her boyfriend?
関係ない私まで いじめられたわけ？
No, I wasn't, Memi! I mean...
芽実 違うの あのね…
You fucking bitch!
ふざけんな！
-Stop it, Memi! -God damn you! You bitch!
（愛奈）芽実 やめて （芽実）ふざけんな バカ！
-Stop! I didn't do it! -You're not my friend!
（愛奈）違う やめて！ （芽実）何が親友だ！
-I didn't do it! -You bitch!
（愛奈）違う！ （芽実）バカ！
-Fuck you!
（芽実）ふざけんな！
-Memi! -God damn you!
（愛奈）芽実…
What are these?
（彩花）え！
What?
（愛奈）え？
Give it back! Please!
返して！ お願い！
-These are all photos of Okazaki. -Give it back!
（彩花）岡崎さんの写真ばっか！ （愛奈）返して！
-Let me see. -Look.
（久美）見せて （彩花）ほら 見て
Give it back!
（愛奈）返して！
Please! Give it back!
お願い お願い！ 返して…
There are photos that aren't from the barbecue.
（彩花） バーベキューのとき以外の 写真がある
-Look at this. -Stop!
（彩花）これ見て （愛奈）やめて！
I'll talk.
話すから…
I'll tell you about it.
ちゃんと話すから…
Please. Give it back.
お願い 返して…
Sorry.
ごめん
I...
私ね…
was in love with Okazaki.
岡崎さんのことが好きだったの
Really?
（芽実）え…
I fell in love with him.
好きになっちゃったの
I thought so.
やっぱり そうなんじゃねえかよ
Kyoko.
（美玲）京子！
When he and Miho started dating,
美穂と岡崎さんが つきあい始めたころ
I ran into them one day.
街で たまたま２人に会って…
The three of us went to a café.
で ３人でカフェに行ったんだけど
That was the time
そのときね 岡崎さん…
Okazaki started calling me by my first name.
私のこと“愛奈ちゃん”って ちゃん付けで呼んでくれて…
That made me fall for him.
それで 好きになったっていうか…
It was love at first sight.
一目ぼれしたっていうか…
There's nothing special about that.
それ 普通だよね？
You fell in love with another girl's boyfriend because of that?
そんなことで 人の彼氏 好きになるか？
Then,
（愛奈）で…
I read through Okazaki's Twitter feed.
岡崎さんのツイッターとか調べて
I went alone to the places where they went on dates.
２人がデートに行った所に １人で行ってみたり…
Really?
え？
I went to the hospital to watch him work.
病院に岡崎さんが働いてる姿を 見に行ってみたり…
What? That's weird.
（久美） え… ちょ ちょっと待ってよ
Do you know the password to Miho's phone?
（愛奈） 美穂のスマホのパスワード 知ってる？
No.
（久美）いや…
Miho
（愛奈）美穂…
made her password the date she and Okazaki started dating, May 3.
岡崎さんと つきあい始めた ５月３日をパスワードにしてて
I accessed Miho's phone and got Okazaki's number.
美穂のスマホから 岡崎さんの携帯番号 調べて…
I made prank calls and hung up several times.
何度か無言電話してみたり…
What a total stalker.
完全にストーカーじゃねえかよ
That's all I did! I swear!
でも 本当にそれだけなの！
"That's all"?
それだけって…
What a bitch.
最低
It was the first time I had fallen in love.
（愛奈） だって 私 人を好きになったのも 初めてだったし
I didn't know what to do.
どうしたらいいか分かんなくて…
During the barbecue, Okazaki served me meat and stuff.
バーベキューの日も 岡崎さん お肉 取ってくれたり…
Our eyes kept meeting.
何度も目が合ったし…
I couldn't hold back my feelings for him any longer.
もう 私 岡崎さんを好きって 気持ちが抑えきれなくなって…
So, when we were leaving, I pulled him aside
それで 帰るとき 岡崎さんを呼び出して…
and told him my feelings.
告白した
I said, "I love you."
“大好きです”って
He turned me down.
フラれたよ
But,
でも…
he said, "I don't hate you though."
岡崎さん 私のこと 嫌いじゃないよって
He only said that because...
いや それは…
Hearing those words made me so happy.
そう言ってくれただけでも 私は すごい うれしくて…
Look, Mana. What he meant was...
（芽実）愛奈 あのね それは…
"I don't hate you" means "I might like you," right?
嫌いじゃないってことは 好きかもしれないってことでしょ！
How can you be so naive? What an idiot.
（京子） お前 純粋すぎるのも いいかげんにしろよ
Don't tell me you're still stalking him.
（彩花） ねえ もしかして 今もストーカー 続けてんの？
I'm not a stalker!
（愛奈） 私はストーカーなんかじゃない！
Yes, you definitely are.
（京子） いや ストーカーだろ どう考えても
Miho doesn't know about that, right?
（久美） その話 美穂は知らないよね？
No.
（愛奈）うん
But, after the barbecue,
でも 私ね
I told Miho about it.
あのバーベキューのあと 美穂に言ったの
I said
あの男は…
Okazaki is
岡崎さんは…
a scumbag boyfriend, and she should break up with him.
最低な彼氏だから 別れたほうがいいって
You lied to her?
（久美）うそついたの？
It wasn't a lie.
うそっていうか…
I wanted him for myself.
だって 私のものにしたかったから
But after that, Miho started bullying me.
でも その日から 美穂に いじめられるようになって…
Before I knew it, I got Memi involved.
気付いたら 芽実まで巻き込まれてて…
That's why we bullied her.
それが 私たちへの いじめの原因
Memi shouldn't be blamed. It's all my fault.
芽実は悪くなくて 私が全部悪いの
I'm sorry, Memi.
芽実 ごめんね
Memi.
芽実…
-Help me! -What's wrong?
（愛奈）助けて！ （美玲）どしたの？
-Water?
（久美）水!? （美玲）水!?
-Mana! -Oh, God!
（芽実）愛奈！ （愛奈）いや！
Oh, God! Help me, Memi!
嫌だ！ 芽実 助けて！
Okazaki! Forgive her!
岡崎さん！ もう許してください！
Please!
お願いします！
No! Okazaki isn't doing this!
違う！ 犯人は岡崎さんじゃない！
How would you know?
え？ どういうこと？
Okazaki broke up with Miho. He has a new girlfriend!
岡崎さん もう美穂とは別れて 新しい彼女がいるの！
What? They broke up?
え？ 美穂とは別れたの？
He would never do this to Miho!
だから 美穂のために こんなこと 絶対にしない！
Where did you learn that?
なんで そんなこと知ってるんだよ？
I know everything about Okazaki!
（愛奈） 私は岡崎さんのことなら 何でも知ってるの！
You bitch!
ずるい！
You're hiding something, but you are just staying silent.
しゃべれないのを いいことに ずっと黙ってて！
What are you talking about?
なに？ 何 言ってるの？
I know all about it!
全部 知ってるんだからね 私！
Are you hiding something, Shiho?
（久美）史帆 何か隠してるの？
Come on! Tell us!
何なんだよ！ 早く言えよ！
You and Okazaki...
あんただって岡崎さんと…
Memi!
（愛奈）芽実 芽実…
Mana!
（芽実）愛奈！
I'm so sorry! It's all my fault!
（愛奈）ごめんね 私のせいで
I can't take this!
（彩花）もうやだ！
Shiho.
史帆
What do you know about Okazaki?
岡崎さんと何があったの？
Come on, Shiho!
ねえ 史帆！
What are you hiding?
何を隠してるの？
That hurt.
（史帆）痛い
What?
（京子）え？
Damn you!
許さない！